我不想夸大事实
Okay, I don't want to overstate this,
但这肯定是最棒的婚礼礼品袋了
but these have to be the best wedding gift bags ever.
根本比不上格温妮斯·帕特洛的婚礼
It's gonna be hard to beat Gwyneth Paltrow's wedding.
我听说他们送的是她的素描肖像
I heard they gave away beautiful charcoal drawings of Gwyneth Paltrow.
真不敢相信 Brooke竟然要结婚了
I can't believe Brooke's getting married.
我们从来没见过这位姓Elliot的家伙
We've never even met this Elliot guy.
真不敢相信 Jane和Alex竟然有一个姐姐
I can't believe Jane and Alex have an older sister.
我们从没见过她 从没提起过她
I mean, we never see her, never talk about her,
- 从没在你们的闪回里出现过 - 闪回?
- she never shows up in any of your flashbacks.- Flashbacks?
那是Jane和Alex照片集的名字
That's what Jane and Alex call their photo albums.
天啊 Penny 只有照片集叫这名字的
God, Penny. Know what things are called for once.
相信我 Brooke真的存在
Trust me, Brooke is very real.
她在香港有份理想的工作
She has a perfect job in Hong Kong.
她的头发有肉桂海滩的味道 她非常完美
Her hair smells like a perfect beach made of cinnamon. She is perfect.
作为伴娘 我想要这场婚礼...
And as maid of honor, I need this wedding to be--
- 跟我一起说 真...完美 - 珍...珠港
- say it with me-- Perfect. - Pearl Harbor.
珍珠港 因为我们想让婚礼充满爆点
Pearl Harbor! 'Cause we want this wedding to be da bomb!
就像迈克尔·贝的电影世界末日一样
Just like that Michael Bay movie "Armageddon."
- 什么 - Jane 你真心要疯啊
- What? - Jane, you're acting extra nuts,
还不是把汤匙当茶匙的那种疯
and I'm not talking about "mistaking the teaspoon with the tablespoon" kinda nuts.
是梅尔·吉布森喝下五小时能量饮料
I'm talking about "Mel Gibson downing a 5-hour energy
然后不小心出现在受戒礼的那种疯
and by accident showing up at a Bar Mitzvah" kinda nuts.
Brooke把Jane逼疯了 她比Jane还要Jane
Brooke makes Jane crazy. She out-Janes Jane.
在她面前 Jane也就是Alex的水平
She shows up, becomes the Jane, Jane gets bumped down to Alex's level.
我就只能做个宝宝
And I just stay the baby.
看Brooke给了我什么 让我不嫉妒她的戒指
Look what Brooke got me so I wouldn't be jealous of her ring.
戒指糖
Oh, a little suck candy.
能被邀请 我就很开心
I'm just glad I got invited.
我一直认识Brooke 而且仰慕她
Like, I've known Brooke my whole life and looked up to her,
但我不知道 她竟然记得我
but I didn't know that she would remember me.
她不记得 你和Max是我带去的
She doesn't. You and Max are my plus-twos
- 你们得帮着客人泊车 - Jane
- and you're gonna have to park some cars. - Jane!
宝贝 不会出问题的 好吗
Babe, everything's gonna be fine, all right?
我会一直陪在你身边
I'll be right by your side.
我甚至允许你那种族歧视的侄子 问我认不认识Blair Underwood
I'll even let your racist cousins ask me if I know Blair Underwood.
好像所有黑人都是朋友似的
Like... like all black people are friends are somethin'.
我是说 拜托
I mean, come on!
天啊 真希望跟他做朋友
God, I wish I was friends with Blair Underwood.
我的软陶珠子做好了
My clay beads are ready!
你们这些家伙想帮我制作几条项链吗
How many of you cool cats wanna help me crank out a few necklaces?
额的神啊
Ohh! Oh, my goodness. Yes, oh, my goodness.
我要制作一些聚合物...
I'm working with some polymers right...
我了个...
Hey. What the...
Alex 我看见你躲在那
Alex, I can see you hiding.
还能看见我吗
Can you still see me?
是的 看得更清楚了
Yes. Even more now.
好吧
Fine!
不过这次已经好多了
Nice try, though.
所以...
So...
咱什么时候告诉大家这件事
When are we gonna tell everybody about the thing?
什么事
What thing?
我们如何分手的事
The thing about how we broke up.
好吧 那件事
Oh, right. That thing.
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业途径
<font color=#29F6E5>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents</font>
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: Melody 力士 狗肉 校对: 王棫垚 时间轴: 有志青年
<font color=#29F6E5>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- Sync: 有志青年</font>
幸福终点站 第三季 第23集
<font color=#29F6E5>Happy.Endings.S03E23</font>
所以就真的发生了
So this is really happening.
我们分手了
We're breaking up.
当你像这样大声说出来时 就都明白了
Yeah, when you say it out loud like that, it just really sinks in.
就像我发现绯闻女孩其实是男的
Like when I found out Gossip Girl was a guy.
完全同意
Totally.
所以我们都同意哈 在你姐结婚前不告诉任何人
So we both agree, we don't tell everyone until after your sister's wedding, right?
是的 肯定会让大家心烦意乱
Yeah, it would be too much of a distraction.
而且我的家人特别爱八卦 他们还总会错意
Plus, my family is so gossipy and they always get the story wrong.
记得吗 有一次你说你喜欢西尼德·玛丽
Remember that one time you said you like Sinead O'Connor,
当消息传了一圈回来时 变成了你在一所女子学院教巫术
and by the time it got back to us, you were teaching Wicca at a women's college?
- 我就告诉过你一个人 - 确实是
- You were the only one that I told. - Exactly.
力量 勇气 镇静 不发牢骚
Strength, courage, composure, no carbs.
我们开始吧
Here we go.
- Brooke - Jane
- Hi, Brooke. - Jane.
- 欢迎来我家 - 谢谢
- Welcome to my home! - Thank you.
- 你肯定就是黑色Elliot了 - 黑色Elliot
- And you must be Black... Elliot. - Black Elliot?
只是外号哈 我们不会再说了
Yes. That's just a nickname that we'll stop using immediately.
谢谢你邀请我们来你家 Jane
Thank you for having us to your home, Jane.
你翻新过了吗
Have you been renovating?
因为所有地方都好像有一小层灰
Because it looks like everything's covered with a thin layer of dust.
眼神不错
Good catch.
我肯定是彻底打扫过了 而不是被迫随便搞搞的
Yeah, I must've just cleaned thoroughly instead of compulsively.
- Brooke - 你好
- Brooke! - Hello.
- 给我一些爱 姑娘 - 很高兴见到你
- Gimme some love, girl. - Nice to see you.
很高兴见到你
So good to see you.
看看你带把什么带回家了
And look what you brought home.
一位Elliot
An Elliot.
- 大家好 - 嗨
- Hello, everyone. - Hi!
- 最终 另外一位Elliot - 是的
- Ah. Finally, another Elliot. - Yeah.
这两年来 我都没跟其他叫Elliot的人玩
I haven't hung out with another Elliot in, like, two years, man.
抱一个
Bring it in.
知道吗 他闻上去也很像叫Elliot的人
You know, he even smells like an Elliot.
这真好
Yeah, this is good.
- 伙计 - 什么
- Hey, yo, E. - Mm?
- 我可以问你一个问题吗 - 什么
- Can I ask you a question, man? - What's up?
我可以问你一个小问题吗
Can I ask you a little somethin' somethin'?
请说
Please do.
如果他们不在周围 我们说什么
What we be sayin' when they ain't around?
我是说 如果他们不在周围 我们会说什么
I said, I said... what we be sayin' when they ain't around?
白人很疯狂吗
White people be crazy?
是的
Yeah, they do!
我就知道你懂
Aah! I knew you gon' know!
但他们的确很疯狂
They do be crazy, though!
- 只是一些人 - 都疯狂
- Some do. - Y'all do.
- 我们去喝点东西吧 我的Elliot - 我同意
- Yeah, let's get you a drink, my Elliot. - All right, I'm with that.
- Brooke - 妹妹
- Brooke! - Little sis!
见到你真高兴
Oh, it's so good to see you.
你给我带了什么
What'd you bring me? What'd you bring me?
中国糯米糖 包装纸可以吃
Chinese rice candy. You can eat the wrapper!
闭嘴
Shut up!
这样好节省时间哦
That'll save me so much time.
- 我爱你 姐姐 - 我也爱你
- I love you, sis. - I love you, too.
- 姑娘 - 嗨
- Hey, girl! - Yay.
嗨 我是Brooke Kerkovich 这是...
Uh, hi, I'm Brooke Kerkovich. It's an...
嗨 好的
Hi. Okay.
Brooke 我是Penny Hartz
Brooke, Penny Hartz!
我经常在你家过夜
I slept over at your house a lot.
七年级时 我写过一篇关于你的文章
Oh, I wrote that paper on you in seventh grade.
你开车撞我 整个夏天我腿都绑着绷带
You hit me with your car, and I had to wear a leg brace all summer.
是的 是哪条腿来着
Oh, yes. That's right. What leg was that again?
左腿
The left.
对不起 我以为是另外一个人
No. Sorry, I'm thinking of someone else.
好吧
Yeah, totally.
我也以为是另外一个人
Yeah, I was thinking of someone else, too.
这么多金发
So much blonde.
过来 坐下
Come on. Sit down.
- 她这人很古怪 - 是的
- She's an odd one. - Yes.
你和爸爸谈过了吗
So have you talked to dad?
难以置信 他竟然食言了
I can't believe he threw his back out.
他没法来 他不会参加婚礼的
He's immobilized. He's not coming to the wedding.
- 我们要延期吗 - 延期? 都到这时候了?
- Should we postpone? - Postpone? At this stage?
- Jane 你在开玩笑吧 - 是的
- Jane, is that a joke? - Yep.
晚宴彩排计划是什么
So... how are the rehearsal dinner plans?
非常好 所有事情都按你的计划进行
Perfect. Everything is done to your specifications.
- 妈妈坐哪里 - 远离乐队的地方
- Where's mom sitting? - Away from the band,
那她就不会试图加入乐队唱歌了
so she doesn't try to join them for a song.
- 花呢 - 低过敏性的
- Flowers? - Hypoallergenic.
如果会流泪 肯定是因为新娘的荣耀
All tears should be caused by the bride's glory.
- 给孩子用的桌子呢 - 没有
- Kids' table? - There isn't one.
孩子们都会被看着 你看不见他们 也听不见他们的声音
Children should be seen and not heard and also not seen.
很好
Good.
妈妈
Hi, mom!
甜心
Well, hi, sweetie.
- Janie - 爸爸
- Hey, Janie! - Hey, dad.
- 感觉怎么样 - 很惊艳
- How you feeling? - Amazing.
你们看过"博物馆惊魂夜"吗
Have you guys seen "Night At The Museum, Battle Of The Smithsonian"?
这可是一部神片
Because it is a masterstroke.
你爸爸正在服用了一堆神奇的药
Your dad's on a lot of fancy pills right now.
他跟平常不一样
He's really not himself.
Barb 转一圈给我看看
Hey, Barb, take me for a spin.
让我看看 我到底为什么鬼地方付了钱
Show me what the hell else I'm paying for in this joint.
- 他还是跟平常差不多 - 是的
- Yep, he's still pretty much himself. - Yeah.
这周末还有其他房间空着吗?
Are there possibly any other rooms available for this weekend?
让我查一下
Let me check.
你怎么又订一间房?
Why do you need another room?
你知道的 Dave跟我...
you know, 'cause Dave and I just...
纵欲过度 需要一间屋冷静下
have so much sex that we need a cooldown room.
得了 没人会纵欲到这种程度
Okay, nobody has that much sex.
你以为你是the Fonz吗?
Who do you think you are, the Fonz?
好吧 我跟Dave上周分手了
Okay, fine. Dave and I broke up last week.
天哪 难以置信 你还好吗
Oh, my God! I can't believe it! Are you okay?
还好吧 我也不知道
Yeah. I think. I don't know.
亲爱的 好遗憾 怎么回事啊
Oh! Sweetie, I'm so sorry. What happened?
我们正说着Brooke婚礼的事
Well, we were talking about Brooke's wedding
- 接着我们就被反锁在卧室里了 - 又被锁了?
- and then we got locked in our bedroom. - Again?
那是老房子了 门自己涨开了 木头分开了 我们傻透了
It's a old building. The doors expand, the wood separates, and we're idiots!
真无法相信Brooke跟这位Elliot 只认识了一年就要结婚
I can't believe Brooke's marrying this Elliot guy after only, like, a year.
不觉得有点快了吗
It's kind of fast, right?
他们之前都谈过恋爱
Well, they both dated a lot of people before they met.
所以当他们认识后 就能感觉到
So when they met each other, they just knew.
就像我看到花状洋葱 我就知道了
Like when I met the bloomin onion, I just knew.
咱们从没跟别人交往过吧
Well, we never really dated anybody else.
我去看看浴室的窗户
I'll check the bathroom window.
你这话什么意思
What-- what do you mean?
我们分手时 也跟别人也谈过啊
I mean, we dated other people during our break.
我那都不算真正的恋爱
Well, I didn't really date.
我会把那叫做与大量美女
I would call it a series of mind-blowing sexual experiences
美妙的性体验 你呢
with a lot of beautiful women. What about you?
- 只有过一个人 让我有过感觉 - 啥?!
- Yeah, I had one guy, like, feel me up. - What?!
我没事 有没有到二垒 管它呢
It's fine. Over or under the bra? Whatever!
他解胸衣技术如何 有什么所谓呢 David
Was he quick with the clasp? Doesn't matter, David.
我觉得我们从未真正分手过
I guess we didn't really have a true break.
基本上我们算是彼此的复合对象
We're basically each other's rebound relationship.
- 你说什么 - 我也不知道
- What are you saying? - I don't know,
Brooke和Elliot之所以知道 他们是彼此的唯一
I mean, Brooke and Elliot knew that they were right for each other
是因为他们以前谈过其他恋爱
'cause they both had other real relationships.
窗户还是卡住的 还是再试试卧室门吧
This window's still jammed. Let's-- let's try the bedroom door again.
拜托
Oh, come on!
看到没 所以我上厕所 从来不关门
See, Dave? This is why I don't shut the bathroom door when I'm in here.
我震惊了
Wow. I am floored. So--
我跟Dave发誓 在婚礼前不跟任何人说的
Shh! Okay, Dave and I swore that we wouldn't tell anyone until after the wedding.
等一下
back up a sec.
这可是大事啊
This is huge.
Alex大泻特泻时 就让厕所门大敞着吗
Alex just lets it rage with the bathroom door open?
- 牛掰啊 - Max
- Baller move! - Max.
抱歉 我只是习惯了你俩分分合合
Sorry. I guess I just got used to you two dummies being back together.
- 你还好吗 - 还好
- You okay? - Yeah. I guess.
从某种意义上说 我挺好的
In a way, it was kinda good.
被迫关在那屋子里几小时
You know, being locked in that room for a couple hours
让我们有时间好好谈谈我们之间的事
really forced us to finally deal with our stuff.
那我们这次是认真的了
So are we really doing this?
是的吧
Yeah, I guess so.
感觉很糟 但觉得应该这么做
It sucks but it feels right.
你不后悔我们复合了吧
You don't regret getting back together, do you?
- 当然不了 - 好的
- No. Of course not. - Okay.
我们要是因为惯性还呆在一起 我才后悔呢
I would've regretted if we stayed together just because of momentum.
那我们又回到刚开始时了
Oh, then we'd be right back where we started.
我不想再经历一次了
I don't want to go through that again.
我都不知道上哪去找 一个穿着旱冰鞋的男人了
I don't even know where I'd find a guy who wears rollerblades anymore.
话别说那么早
Too soon.
咱们赶紧出去吧
Let's get out of here.
- 好 - 我这次是认真的
- Yep. - I mean, really.
什么
What?
不是吧 拜托 我们到底为什么要关这扇门啊
Seriously? Come on! Why'd we close this door anyway?
- 感觉不错 - 你说的对 真的不错
- It felt right! - You're right. It did.
我是塑模协会的持卡会员
Oh, yeah, I'm a card-carrying member of the lami-nation.
我们甚至有自己的宪法 我们自己都不能修订...
We even have our own constitution, which can't we amend...
因为宪法也被塑模了
'cause it's laminated.
塑模会不会太...俗气了
Isn't laminating just a bit... tacky?
如果是东西洒在上面 那怎么办
W-w--what about for spills and stuff?
那不如努力别让东西洒在上面 如何
How about instead of protecting it from spills, we just don't spill, right?
好的
Yeah. Yes.
好主意 Brooke 提醒得好
That's a good idea. You-- good note, Brooke!
塑模 Jane
Lamination, Jane?
你怎么不干脆在上面撒金粉呢 俗逼
Why don't you just cover it in glitter, you...  cheap whore?
- 你好啊 同性恋先生 - 你好啊 伯爵夫人
- Hello, gay sir. - Hello, Countess Vonboobs.
我有个秘密 但我不能告诉你
I have a secret, but I shan't be telling you.
我也有个秘密
I have a secret as well,
而且是很惊天动地的秘密
and it's a real doozie kurtz.
我的秘密很厉害的 一点透露都惊天动地
My secret's so big, just the tip will be enough.
Alex和Dave分手了 你的秘密是不是比这还厉害
Yes, well, is your secret bigger than the fact that Alex and Dave broke up?
- 你妹的 拜托 Max - 那是我的秘密 你妹的 Penny
- Damn it, Max! Come on. - That was my secret, too! Damn it, Penny!
为啥别人都爱把事情告诉我们呢
Why do people tell us stuff?
你们刚刚是不是说Alex和Dave分手了
Did I hear you say that Alex and Dave are breaking up?
抱歉 我是Alex第二个表姐Sherry
I'm sorry. I'm Alex's second cousin Sherry.
不 我们没那么说 你应该是听错了
No. Actually, we did not say that. I think you might've heard wrong.
是这样 Sherry... Alex和Dave并没有分手 他们在...
Y-you see, Sherry... Alex and Dave are not so much breaking up as they are
- 分...房 - 分...房
- breaking... ground. - Breaking... ground.
他们在房间另分出一间
Ground on an addition on their home.
他们要组建家庭啦
Are they starting a family?
因为我在洗手间听到 有人说怀孕的事
Because I knew that I heard someone talking about a pregnancy in the bathroom.
- Sherry 这么跟你说... - Sherry 这么跟你说...
- Sherry, I gotta tell ya... - Sherry, I gotta tell ya...
- 不 - 你的鼻子最灵了
- No. - You're on the nose here.
可以当神探了 神探夏洛克Sherry
Detective work is great. Sherlock Sherry.
他们有孩子了 精子让卵子受孕了
They're pregnant. Super preggers. Sperm has fertilized the egg.
现在呢 她的子宫正在生长厚厚的子宫壁
Right now, her uterus is creating a nutrient-rich lining
好给小小的胚胎一个生长的环境
to house and protect the young fetus.
帮我个忙吧 Sher亲
But do me a favor, Sher Bear?
不如当作这是我们仨的小秘密吧
Why don't we just keep this a secret between the three of us, huh?
好极了
Great.
锁上 把钥匙扔掉
Turn it and throw it away.
你怎么可以造那么大的谣
How could you start a rumor like that?!
你怎么会知道那么多自宫的事情
And how do you know so much about uteruses?
是子宫 你还是女人呢
Uteri. You're a woman.
你应该知道小孩子 是从屁股下面哪里出来的
You should know which part of the butt the baby comes from.
听着 这秘密不能传出去
Look, this secret cannot get out.
现在呢 我感觉这边有很多目光射过来
And right now, I'm feeling a lot of heat in our direction.
我们需要反射回去 改变新闻导向
We need to deflect it. Change the news cycle.
- 难道你跟我想到一起去了 - Penny 打住
- I was sniffin' what you were whiffin'. - Penny, don't.
看看他 Elliot轻轻松松就人缘这么好
Look at him. Elliot's got it so easy...
都是因为我在之前做的工作
because of all the work I did.
我忍受了他们那些奇奇怪怪的问题
I put up with all their weird questions
使得他们习惯了一个黑人在旁边
and made them feel comfortable around a black guy.
天哪
Oh, my God.
我是Kerkovich家族的Jackie Robinson
I'm the Jackie Robinson of the Kerkovich family.
你还真抬举自己
Sure. That's not a leap at all.
我扫除了障碍 好吗
I broke down barriers, okay?
Elliot也应该经受下我的那些磨难
And Elliot should have to go through what I did.
Jackie Robinson真正的功绩
Actually, the true legacy of Jackie Robinson
是让Elliot不用经受你的那些磨难
is that Elliot shouldn't have to go through what you did.
我记得Medgar Evers曾经说过
I believe it was Medgar Evers who once said--
伙计 我们懂了 你辅修了黑人历史
Dude, we get it. You minored in black history.
非裔美国人学
Afro-American studies.
你说辅修(minor) 简直太不礼貌了 (minor也有少数人种的意思)
And I am offended by your use of the term "minor."
现在不是来这套的时候
Now is not the time, man!
好了 Berg医生 我知道咱家的孩子都是你接生的
All right, Dr. Berg, I know you delivered every child in this family,
但是您坐错位置了
but you're in the wrong seat.
我希望您能像George Clinton那样 从这里走开
So I'm gonna need you to make like George Clinton and get the funk outta here.
- Jane - 怎么了
- Jane. - Yeah?
你干嘛跟B医生过不去
Why are you freaking out on Dr. B?
因为座位表弄坏了 所以每个人都坐错了位置
Because I put everyone in the wrong place because the seating chart is ruined.
- 什么 - 我把座位表去了模
- What? - I had to unlaminate it,
然后我就满身大汗 只有Brooke来的时候我才这样
and then I got those weird sweats that I only get when Brooke's around.
怪不得妈跑到乐队那边去了
Well, that explains why mom ended up by the band.
看来座位完全乱了套
So... the seating is a complete mess,
我觉得那女人根本不该出现在这里
and I'm pretty sure that woman doesn't even belong here.
我第一次用卫生棉 就是你给买的
You bought me my first maxi pad.
Jane 我很清楚你现在压力过大
Jane, it's very clear to me that the pressure is getting to you,
我觉得还是给你安排一个简单点的工作
and I think we need to give you a simpler task.
放手 放手
Let go. Let go.
你明天不用帮我准备了
Instead of helping me get ready tomorrow,
你还是去发节目单好了
I think it would be better if you handed out programs.
- 至于你... - 啊?
- And you... - Yeah?
你表现得很不错
are doing a wonderful job.
谢谢
Thank you.
你...安排得不错
Y-you-- yeah, that's a good plan.
冒昧问下 你还好吗
Aw, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- 挺好的 - 那就好
- I'm good. - Okay.
真的挺好 其实我要去查看一下
I'm really good. Yeah. I gotta-- actually, I gotta check on...
- 那行 - 那边一些事
- Okay. - The... thing in the...
好了哟 大块头 挪挪地方
All right. Okay, big boy, let's go. Let's go!
真的吗 Elliot认识Blair Underwood
Are you serious? Elliot knows Blair Underwood?
是的 他还很喜欢别人问起这事
Oh, yeah. And he loves it when people ask him about it.
他来了
Here he comes.
Elliot 你认识Blair Underwood吗
Hey, Elliot. You know Blair Underwood?
搞什么
What? What?!
我的天啊
Oh, my gosh!
难道所有黑人都认识Blair Underwood吗
Like all black people are just supposed to know Blair Underwood, huh?
实际上 我确实认识Blair
actually, I do know Blair.
他人非常好 是我们慈善机构的发言人
He's a great guy. He's a spokesman for a charity I work with.
这可太牛了 Elliot
Wow! That is very impressive, Elliot.
肯定有不少故事可以讲讲吧
The stories you must have, huh?
搞什么 不能这样
What? No!
都是些蠢事 我才是牛人
The-- stories are stupid! I'm impressive!
我是Jackie Robinson
I'm Jackie Robinson!
Alex...怎么喝酒呢
So, Alex... drinking, huh?
考虑到你现在的情况 是不是不太...
In your condition? Isn't that--
这在欧洲还是很合适的吧 是的
Uh, acceptable in Europe? Yes.
- 你带着浓浓的法式风情 Alex - 说得没错
- How very French of you, Alex. - I guess it is.
Ooh, la la! Pepe le pew! French Stewart!
- Alex 胃口怎么样  - 好到爆
And, Alex, how are your cravings? Insane.
好到爆 谢谢问候
Totally insane. Thank you for asking.
这可是少见
this rarely happens.
我总觉得错过了什么
I feel like I'm missing something.
就像是那时 人们突然对亚麻裤着迷
Like that time that everybody turned on linen pants all of a sudden.
没没 我不觉得
No. No. No. No, I don't,
好吧 我们该怎么办
Okay, what are we gonna do?
我们得再次改变新闻导向
We need to change the news cycle again.
有办法了
I have an idea.
快过来一下 Sher
Scuttle your butt on over here, Sher.
有一条顶级八卦 但你不能说出去 行吗
I got some grade-A goss, but you have it keep it a secret. Okay?
Jane和Brad正闹分手
Jane and Brad are on the rocks.
你明白我的意思了吗
You tastin' what I'm wastin'?
- Pen 别说了 - 只是别告诉任何人
- Pen, come on. - Just... just don't tell anybody.
保证守口如瓶
Oh! Your secret's safe with me.
这招可要奏效啊 Max
This better work, Max.
耐心等待
Give it time. Give it time.
听好了 跟你们透露一个秘密
So this is hush-hush,
Brad有私生子了 所以Brad和Jane正闹离婚
but Brad and Jane are divorcing because Brad has a love child.
传播得真快
Wow. That was fast.
流言蜚语满天飞呀
They really took it and ran.
添油加醋 不胫而走
Yeah, but you know what I liked? They really made it their own.
你好
Hello.
不要折叠 那不是垃圾
Do not fold that! It's not garbage.
那是下午精彩活动的介绍指南
It's a guide to your magical afternoon.
Brooke听说 你好像对来宾不太友善
Hey, um, so Brooke heard that you were making people feel uncomfortable.
所以她打算直接把册子放桌子上
So she thought it'd be better if you just let the podium do your job.
- 放桌子上 - 不好意思 我只是...
- The podium? - Sorry, Jane. I just--
我也只是运气好
I lucked out that, you know,
- 我天生就是做撒花女的份 - 是啊...
- I was born for this whole flower girl gig. - Yeah...
撒花的时机和方式都太不靠谱了
It's not at all how or when you're supposed to do that.
Brooke女士 Elliot先生 重要时刻到了
Brooke, Elliot, we've reached the big moment.
Elliot 你愿意Brooke成为你的妻子吗
Elliot, do you take Brooke to be your lawfully wedded wife?
- 我愿意 - 不要 不要
- I do. - Ohh. No, no, no, no.
Brooke 你愿意让Elliot成为你的丈夫吗
And do you, Brooke, take Elliot to be... your lawfully wedded husband?
- 不要 - 什么
- No! - What?!
不不 不是说它们 起火了
No, no, not them. There is a fire,
手册着火了
and... programs are on fire.
大家都在这别动 我是消防志愿者
Everyone stay here. I'm a volunteer firefighter.
我是消防志愿者
I'm a volunteer firefighter.
继续炫耀你的工作经历吧 老兄
Keep reading us your resume, dude.
Dave 带Alex出去
Dave, get Alex out of here.
烟雾对小孩子不好
The fumes are bad for the baby.
在家里 我确实算小孩子 但我是成年人
I know I'm the baby of the family, but I'm a big girl!
我能走出玉米迷宫 逃出这里更不在话下
If I can get through a corn maze, I can get out of here.
不是 我是说你肚子里怀的宝宝
No, the baby you're having.
- 什么 - 什么
- What? - What?
- 不是的 Brad和Jane才有宝宝了 - 什么
- No, it's Brad and Jane that are having the baby. - What?!
不是的 那是Brad和某女人的野种
No! It's a love child that Brad has with some floozy.
- 所以他们才闹离婚的 - 什么
- That's why they're getting divorced. - What?!
- 什么 - 我哪有什么私生子
- What? - I'm not having a love child!
那究竟是谁分手了
Well, then who's breaking up?
- 是我跟Dave - 什么
- Dave and I are. - What?
我知道 我本该早告诉你们
I know. I... We should've told all of you sooner, but...
但其他谣言 我毫不知情
I have no idea where these other stories came from.
Max和Penny告诉我们的
Max and Penny told us.
- 这样啊 - 那就对了
- Okay, well... - Right.
我也是情非得已 必须改变新闻导向
Look, I'm sorry. I had to change the news cycle,
正如我告诉大家Penny已经53岁了
like how I told everyone Penny was 53.
不是吧 大家都不惊讶吗
Oh, come on! No gasps on that?!
那我在厕所听说有人怀宝宝 什么情况
Well, then who did I overhear talking about a baby in the bathroom?
一定是Kerkovich家的女儿
I know it's a Kerkovich girl.
- 不是我 - 不是我
- It wasn't me. - It was not me.
是我 行了吧
It's me. All right?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
Brooke 婚礼太赞了
Brooke, the ceremony was lovely!
您是哪位
Who are you?
你还好吗
How you holding up?
奉子成婚 还伴有瓢泼大雨
Well, my shotgun wedding got soaked.
确实
Yeah.
听着 我知道在你心中 我是完美的
Look, I know you think I'm perfect,
但实际上 我并非完人
but I'm actually not.
- 高兴了吧 - 不高兴
- Happy? - No.
高兴 很高兴
Yes. Very much.
一直以来 我对你很苛刻
I know I've always been a little bit hard on you,
但那是因为 我觉得你很有潜力
but it's because I knew how much potential you had.
我知道你可以很优秀
I knew you could be great.
甚至可能比我还优秀
Maybe even better than me.
所以我以前会打击你
That's why I had to destroy you.
这是你对我说过最中听的话了
That is the nicest thing you have ever said to me.
实话实说
Well, you deserve it.
而且你还只是稍稍毁了我的婚礼
Plus, you only sort of ruined my wedding.
毁了我婚礼的是Max和Penny
Max and Penny really ruined it.
她记得我的名字 太棒了
She remembered me! Yes!
再来一句 真为你感到高兴
Again, I'm so happy for you.
- 嘿 E - 兄弟
- Hey, yo, E. - Hey, man.
听着 我只是想让你知道
listen, I just wanna let you know
很高兴你要加入我们家庭
that I'm really happy to have you in the family.
谢谢了
Oh, thanks.
你是家里的第一个黑汉子 确实为我铺了路
And look, I know you being here first did make it easier for me.
不过你让Kerkovich未婚先孕了
although, now that you've knocked up a Kerkovich daughter out of wedlock...
- 前路会很艰难 - 明白
- you're gonna have it plenty rough. - Yeah.
所以我会一直挺你的
So I'm here for you, man.
- 自家兄弟 - 自家兄弟
- Brother-in-law. - Brothers-in-law.
Elliot 我们得谈谈
Elliot, we need to talk.
你有麻烦了
Ohh! You in trouble!
开始吧 美女
Do it, girl.
恭喜你 Elliot 我们家第一个孙子
Congratulations, Elliot. Our first grandchild.
我和Barb高兴坏了
Barb and I are thrilled!
Brad必定要很久才能让他老婆怀孕
It sure is taking Brad long enough.
让人不禁怀疑他的能力
It makes you wonder what's wrong with his stuff.
我能力方面没问题 别担心我的能力
My stuff is fine! Don't worry about my stuff!
- 他能力肯定没问题 - 强着呢
- I'm sure his stuff if okay. - It's excellent!
这首送给有宝宝的妈妈们
Aw, yeah! This one goes out to the baby mamas,
以及没有宝宝的妈妈们 真情侣们 假情侣们 兄弟姐妹们
the not baby mamas, the couples, the fake couples, the brothers, the sisters,
还有那位用一次性相机的帅哥哥
and one handsome genius that took a single loving peen pic
with every disposable camera in this room
祝贺Brooke和Elliot新婚愉快
Congratulations, Brooke and Elliot!
你显然是跟哪位浪女有了私生子
So apparently you're having a love child with some tramp.
我只会跟你生私生子
Boo, the only tramp I'm ever gonna put a love child in is you.
那会很有趣的
That is gonna be so fun.
只要比Brooke和Elliot的孩子好就行
As long as it's better than Brooke and Elliot's.
那是
Yes.
你还好吗
How ya doin'?
我很好
I'm good.
我们现在是正式单身了
Hey, you know, we're officially on the market now.
不如我帮你找一个舞伴吧
How about I find you a dance partner?
她怎么样
Her?
不中意吗
No?
那她呢 她显然很会跳舞呢
Or her? She has clearly... got grind on the mind.
这样说吧 我觉得今晚
You know what? I think tonight,
就想和我朋友跳支舞
I just wanna dance with my friend.
我也正有此意
Yeah, I'd like that.
幸福终点站 第三季 第23集 -=本剧终=-
<font color=#29F6E5>-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents</font>